ASYRAF DUYSHART

FULLSTACK MOBILE DEVELOPER / DESIGNER / PHILOSOPHER

I am known as a young entrepreneur, designer, developer, consultant, public speaker, writer and philosopher.

I have 7+ years of experiences in organisation engagement and community development since high school, 5+ years in non-profit leadership and management, 2+ years in Digital Startup and 4+ years in mobile Android Development, I started technology interest organisation in high school known as Ubiquity Cyber School, founding and create Startup like GalauCerdas, Solutalk, Persona and Klik Tukang

I specialise in UI/UX Design and develop things in Mobile and Web (Yes! I am a lethal combination of Developer + Designer) and love about Computer Software. I'm passionate about what I do, and I love to help people.

Nothing is more fulfilling than being part of a team with similar interests, and an organisation that values its employees. Practical, pragmatic, insightful, prefer progressive & beyond-the-box approach; rather than conservative approach.

I sold my soul to capitalism, mortgage my heart to humanism.

Name	Asyraf Duyshart
Date of birth	September 27, 1992
Address	Jatibening, Bekasi

Email	me@asyraf.id
Phone	+ 62 8788 1141 788
Skype	asyrafduyshart

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

CLEAN ANDROID DEVELOPMENT

NODE.JS

JAVA

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

PREMIERE

RESPONSIBLE

CREATIVE

TEAM PLAYER

CODING

EXPERIENCE



Lead Android Developer - Klik Tukang

🗂 June 2016 - Current

Handle everything in terms of Android Mobile Development. UI, Data flow, mock API, performance and security.

I am using Dagger 2 dependency injection, Retrofit 2 Networking API, and Hardcore RxJava programming paradigm and style.

IT Project Manager - PT. Gapcer Sahabat Muda 🗂 Jan 2013 - Current

Taking care of any IT related project from client Build infrastucture and architecturing project

Designer - Indosat

Aug 2010 - Sept 2011

Design advertising content needed by marketing

EDUCATION



Bachelor of Technology - Gunadarma University 2011 - 2015

High School - SMAN 44 Jakarta Sept 2015 - Nov 2015

SERVICES



CLEAN ANDROID DEVELOPMENT

I used set of very best practice for development in Android, check out my github here



I make a very perfomant and secure

SERVER WITH NODE.JS

server with Node.js, check my github here



ADVANCE ANALYTICS

I could make an very thorough analytics for your bussiness in both interaction in Mobile and Server using Firebase and bigQuery



I understand development method

and framework with Agile methodoly like Scrum



products for customers based on design aestethics and experience based on data experiment

I understand of making a good



I love to make ideas that help people

with current technologies dependency applies

AWARD & ACHIEVEMENT

LIGA DIGITAL INDONESIA BEST APPS PERSONA

Best Mobile Apps competition for Persona. Persona is chat application that connect anonymous user for share

.

